C343 Summer 2018
Homework 3
Ian Polito
ipolito

Task B
	1. For 100000 iterations it took 14 milliseconds.
	3. The mergeTwoLists method works by taking two LList<E> objects that are assumed to be sorted and loops through
	the lists until both have no more elements to add values to a new LList<E> object to be returned. The elements
	are cast as Comparable so they can be compared since LList is a generic class, then the compareTo function is
	used to determine which element of one of the two lists should be added first in order to keep the return list
	sorted.
	4. For the most part CircularLList functions in the same way a double linked list works. I used the same
	constructors for LList but the instance variables are only a reference to the head of the list and the list size.
	This simplifies much of the class and doesn't rely on a current position to insert and remove. I also modified
	the toString method accordingly. The main thing that needed to be changed was the insert and remove methods. For
	the insert method, a new link is made with the given value and the method checks if head is null (empty list). In
	this case, the head is set to this new link and its next and prev references are set to itself to maintain
	circularity. Otherwise, a temporary variable is made to keep track of the old head and the new head is made to
	be the new link. Then the new link's next reference is set to be temp's and its prev reference is set to be temp's
	prev reference. Lastly, the temp's prev reference is set to be the new link and it and temp's prev reference's next
	reference is set to be the new link. All of this inserts the new value at the start of the list and maintains
	circularity. The remove method takes the value of the link to be removed. It first checks if the head's value is
	equal to the one being removed and removes it if so, if not a temporary link is made to search through the list.
	Temp starts at head.next() and loops through until temp is equal to head (to account for circularity) and checks
	each link if it's value is equal to the value to be removed and removes that link if it is.